<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Anthony Wong</title><link>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Anthony Wong</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 22:38:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alcholism</title><link>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/something-new/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 22:38:55 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/something-new/</guid><description>alcoholism is a mental illness, and these are people whose experiences of discrimination and abuse are not known in law in most states and U.S. populations.
What is Sexual Offender Rehabilitation with an Misdemeanor?
Sexual offenders need psychiatric help, counseling and supportive family, friends and family. Some people who have committed severe or ongoing crimes, as well as those with other serious criminal histories, may be offered assistance with any form of legal relief.</description></item><item><title>An Industrial Society</title><link>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/my-fourth-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 17:38:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/my-fourth-post/</guid><description>Industrial society and it&amp;rsquo;s consequences for the rest of the population.
&amp;ldquo;The people themselves don&amp;rsquo;t want this, because they won&amp;rsquo;t be able to live under these conditions and they don&amp;rsquo;t want the people to get together and take responsibility. Instead of working together, you have to bring down prices and make sure there&amp;rsquo;s competition. That&amp;rsquo;s why these prices are increasing.&amp;rdquo;
At the government&amp;rsquo;s disposal is a plan to reduce VAT on imports such as cigarettes, shoes and watches, but it would also make it much easier for ordinary taxpayers.</description></item><item><title>A New View of the Universe</title><link>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/my-third-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 17:36:21 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/my-third-post/</guid><description>Particle physics says they have a good view into the matter- of how particles interact. If you looked closer than 90 degrees you&amp;rsquo;d be right away and you&amp;rsquo;d get your whole body moving.
But instead, the data you&amp;rsquo;re trying to extract from the light is mixed in. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it looks in space:
A small part of the data you&amp;rsquo;re trying to extract is also mixed in. To be clear, the data in your sample were not collated into much larger files.</description></item><item><title>Artificial Intelligence</title><link>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/my-second-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 17:34:58 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/my-second-post/</guid><description>AI, a local NGO that is seeking the rescue of the missing passengers of passenger planes including a passenger plane belonging to Boeing. The plane was shot down in the east Indian Ocean on Saturday. (IBN)
The incident occurred when Malaysia Airlines Flight 14 was approaching a runway in Bangkok, Thailand (AFP Photo/IAN)
The plane, shot down in the east, was in its last flight to the Indian Ocean, while the crew of the A320 plane at the controls were reportedly injured.</description></item><item><title>Computer Science Is...</title><link>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 17:03:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Computer Science and Engineering at University of California, Irvine, who&amp;rsquo;s currently a research fellow on biological sciences at the Institute for Science Education and Technology at The Johns Hopkins University and served as the lead author on the paper.
He said, &amp;ldquo;In this context, the potential therapeutic value of the compound may be significant.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Clinical trial results have shown that tDCS can improve behavior, alleviate cognitive deficit, improve function and improve motor performance in children who have a history of ADHD,&amp;rdquo; Dr.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/page/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logan-lieou.github.io/AnthonyWong/page/about/</guid><description>My name is professor Anthony Wong. I am a graduate student (and also a PhD student). My field of study is computational engineering and systems science. I am a guest lecturer on the Department of Industrial Engineering and has several graduate/post doctoral courses on some topics. So please allow me to add some useful information.
If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about joining a project and have some very useful information or questions you can contact me by email (anthony.</description></item></channel></rss>